<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
  <content>
    <title>Satisfying Videos</title>
    <paragraph>We are here to serve your video spokesperson needs. The exceptional quality of our videos is matched by our spokespeople's talent and our production staff's dedication to ensuring your satisfaction.</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-picture-o</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Website Spokesperson</title>
    <paragraph>As the online face of your business, a video spokesperson can deliver the exact message you want your visitors to hear. Our web spokesperson actors will impress your customers and increase your bottom line</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-user-o</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Greet Your Visiters</title>
    <paragraph>A virtual spokesperson is the best way to interact with website visitors like never before. With our borderless and transparent video technology, you can create the illusion of a real person standing on your webpage and greeting your visitors. Our combination of price and quality is unmatched, so get started today.</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-picture-o</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Video Solutions</title>
    <paragraph>There are other companies you can choose who charge higher prices and require complex setup solutions for their website spokesperson videos. We focus on providing a low cost solution! If you want a high-quality and fairly priced video spokesperson solution to build trust with customers and increase sales, we are the only choice.</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-video-camera</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Installation for Your Spokesperson</title>
    <paragraph>Adding our videos to your website is very easy. Just upload the files we give you and paste in our simple html code. We're happy to help you with installation, free of charge.</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-server</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Transparent Background</title>
    <paragraph>Our videos appear on laptops and desktops with a transparent background so your website will be visible directly behind the body of the model. This creates the illusion of a person actually standing inside your website!</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-user-o</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Amazing Features</title>
    <paragraph>We offer amazing features at the lowest price. Compare our features with the competition, and decide for yourself! Host our videos. If you want us to host the video for you, that's free too!</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-line-chart</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>No Branding</title>
    <paragraph>There is NO branding on our video player. We offer clean, unbranded videos at no additional cost. This feature will only be available for a limited time. We plan to add our branding to future videos products, so if you need an unbranded video, order asap!</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-square</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>We let you Host your files</title>
    <paragraph>We let you host the video files wherever your existing website is already hosted for FREE. Our videos will work with ANY regular hosting service. Nothing special is required to host our videos. If you want us to host the video for you, that's free too!</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-server</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Our Spokespeople</title>
    <paragraph>Our spokespeople are experienced professionals with a wide-range of backgrounds and training in spokesmodeling, acting, broadcast journalism, television, on camera promotions, and live performance.</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-user-o</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Transparent Video</title>
    <paragraph>A video spokesperson is a spokesperson who appears on a website to greet visitors. On Laptops and Desktops our Video Spokesperson features a transparent background, resulting in the appearance of a borderless video of a person standing on a website.</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-video-camera</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Professional Spokespeople</title>
    <paragraph>People use many terms for Spokespeople: Video Spokesperson, Virtual Spokesperson, Website Spokesperson, Web Spokesperson, Spokes-model, Walk On Actor, Virtual Actor, Person on website, Online Spokesperson.</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-user-o</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Customer Service</title>
    <paragraph>We are committed to all of our customers. Our friendly and knowledgeable video specialists will happily answer any questions you have and help you with your video needs before, during, and after the quick and easy ordering process. In fact, if you need our assistance with setting up the video on your website, we'll help you free of charge!</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-comments-o</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Quality Videos</title>
    <paragraph>We pride ourselves on our high quality and successful actors and actresses and all our videos are all shot and built here at our headquarters to maintain quality and precision. It is all filmed HERE.</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-video-camera</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>What is a Web Spokesperson</title>
    <paragraph>People use a variety of terms to describe a website spokesperson. These include: video spokesperson, talking video, website avatar, talking greeter, virtual greeter, walk-on actor, virtual presenter, website greeter, transparent video, virtual face on web, web spokesmodel, online salesperson, etc.</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-user-o</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Welcome Visitors</title>
    <paragraph>Add a Spokesperson to your website to welcome visitors and direct them to key areas. Increase conversion rates and boost leads. Uses HTML5 canvas for Transparent effect, but when detects mobile device uses standard MP4.</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-comment-o</icon>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Our Spokespeople</title>
    <paragraph>Our spokespeople are experienced professionals with a wide-range of backgrounds and training in spokesmodeling, acting, broadcast journalism, television, on camera promotions, and live performance. Our models are ready to put their talent and positive energy into promoting your product or service.</paragraph>
    <icon>fa-user-o</icon>
  </content>
</data>
