<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://www.live-spokesperson.com/generator/pages/mods/sitemap.xsl"?>
<urlset
      xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
      xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1"
      xsi:schemaLocation="
            http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9
            http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9/sitemap.xsd">
<!-- created with Standalone Sitemap Generator www.xml-sitemaps.com (48290) -->

  <url>
       <loc>http://www.live-spokesperson.com/</loc>
       <lastmod>2019-02-16T01:20:05+00:00</lastmod>
       <changefreq>daily</changefreq>
       <priority>1.0000</priority>
       <video:video>
         <video:thumbnail_loc>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/2EhlppFns_w/mqdefault.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc> 
         <video:title>Why Talking Heads Typography</video:title>
         <video:description>Why Talking Heads Typography
https://www.websitetalkingheads.com/typography/
Talking Heads® can create an engaging, professional Kinetic Typography Video for your next video project.  Visit http://websitetalkingheads.com/typography/ to learn more.

Kinetic typography refers to the creation of moving text in video form. It is a group of animation techniques that are used to make words bounce, grow, shrink, fly, move quickly or slowly, change color and many other ways for the viewer. The effect can be simple and short with only small changes or quite elaborate and lengthy. Kinetic typography puts this together with some simple animations to create words that move on the screen, grabbing your attention and engaging the senses.
#videoproduction
#customvideo
#webvideo
#videoSEO
👉 Most Recent Upload➩https://goo.gl/VaVe3m
🔥Most Popular Upload➩https://goo.gl/PLjeU3
👍🏼Subscribe to our channel➩https://goo.gl/73T5Vz
It’s a great marketing vehicle for those looking to send a message without losing their audience.

Visit our Google+ page: https://plus.google.com/u/0/104534067803139933846/posts

For more information on Kinetic Typography Videos go to: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kinetic_typography
Website Talking Heads 
245 W. 9000 S. 
Sandy, UT 84070 
801-748-2281
Sales@WebsiteTalkingHeads.com
Visit http://www.WebsiteTalkingHeads.com to buy your custom Video.
Kinetic typography is the specialized name meant for &quot;moving text&quot;—is an animation strategy blending movement along with the copy to express ideas by using video animation. The following text is provided over time in the approach intended to convey or even stimulate an actual approach and also experience. Kinetic typography will come in many designs and versions. Of your house a great honor to a legendary video, speech, or even song you select, and a particular pursuit in the typography by itself, these efforts undoubtedly are a banquet for your eyes. See lively fonts become active in these fantastic Kinetic Typography Videos.

-~-~~-~~~-~~-~-
Please watch: &quot;Element 3d Animation - Typography Example with Optical Flares&quot; 
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5USZK4vuZkU
-~-~~-~~~-~~-~-</video:description>
         <video:publication_date>2018-04-05T03:13:22.000Z</video:publication_date>
         <video:player_loc allow_embed="yes" autoplay="ap=1">http://www.youtube.com/v/2EhlppFns_w</video:player_loc>
         <video:duration>112</video:duration>
       </video:video>
  </url>
</urlset>